My name is Oliver Queen.
我叫Oliver Queen
After five years on a hellish island,
vu上地z般的五年後
I have come home with only one goal...
我回砹 心岩目...
to save my city.
拯救@座城市
But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
但榇宋也荒茉傧褚郧耙⒙
To honor my friend's memory, I must be someone else.
榱思赖煳业暮糜 我必重塑自己
Thomas Merlyn之墓 1985-2013
Thomas Merlyn之墓 1985-2013
I must be something else.
我必窝b自身
Previously on "Arrow"...
"G箭b" 前情提要...
Time to choose, Oliver.
做Q定了 Oliver
Who lives and who dies.
l生l死
Because in 30 seconds, I will shoot them both.
因樵龠^30秒 我就把她z都⒘
You got what you came for!
你的目的已_到了!
I guess you made your choice. Time's up.
看砟氵x好了 rg到
No!
不!
If you stick that in me, I'll kill you.
你敢o我注射 我就⒘四
No, brother Roy, you'll kill for me.
不 Roy兄弟 你槲⒙
Where'd you get the mirakuru?
你哪牡玫狡孥E的?
It was a gift. A gift I would use
@是一份Y物 我要用它
to save this city from itself.
拯救@座城市
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
-=}城家@SCG字幕M http://hd.cnscg.com/=- H供翻g交流使用, 禁止用於商I用途
协调: Tracy 时间轴: 潇妹纸 翻译: 初见 yjk8654 水果哥 Tracy 校对: 潇妹纸
f{: Tracy rgS: t妹 翻g: 初 yjk8654 水果哥 Tracy 校: t妹
Whoa, oh, ahh!
哇 啊!
Ahh! Oh!
啊! 哦!
The man in the skull mask, who is he?!
骷t面具的男人是l?! 快f
I-I don't know!
我不知道!
You're the biggest street dealer in crescent circle.
你是@Y街^最大的毒
You know everything that goes on over there.
@Yl生的一切你都t如指掌
Who is he?!
他是l?!
I ain't seen the guy before!
我以前]^他!
A skull mask, are you freaking kidding me?!
е骷t面具 我真的不知道!
Come on, man, I'm still on parole!
e@ 我在假期!
Not anymore.
Y束了
绿箭侠 第二季第十集
G箭b 第二季第十集
A spokesman for the central city mayor's office confirmed
中心城市Ll言人已C
the lack of any damage or radioactive fallout
五周前S.T.A.R.室l生的爆炸
from the explosion that rocked S.T.A.R. Labs five weeks ago.
K未造成放射性m埃露
Is Felicity not back yet?
Felicity]回?
She said she wanted to spend a few more days with Barry.
她f想再照Barry滋
Any improvement in his condition?
他的情r有好D了?
Still comatose.
在昏迷
How'd it go out there tonight?
今天晚上收如何?
Same as every other pointed conversation
c前滋煸谛略鲁堑
I have with these lowlifes in Crescent circle.
那些下三Ef的一
Nobody...
]人...
has seen a man in a skull mask.
^е骷t面具的人
But he's still out there.
但他在逍b法外
Oliver, for the past five weeks,
Oliver ^去的五周
you've pushed yourself pretty hard looking for this guy.
你用M全力想要找到那人
He has the mirakuru, Diggle!
奇E他手上 Diggle!
I mean, you saw what it took to kill one guy
你^要⒌舯蛔⑸涞娜
that had been injected.
是多N不容易
We practically had to drop a building on him.
要用一大遣拍嚎逅
So imagine ten or a hundred,
所以如果他有十人 一百人
imagine a thousand.
一千人 怎Nk
You said Roy was injected.
你fRoy被注射了
Yeah.
是的
I've just never seen you spooked like this before.
我]看^你@N恐
That should tell you something.
有件事告V你
Shado always told me that I wouldn't die here.
Shado是ξ艺f 我不死在@Y
But looking back, I realized
但回^想想 我lF
that she never once said that about herself.
她]有ψ约赫f^@句
Shado之墓
Shado之墓
I just hope she's with her father now.
希望她和她爸爸F聚了
Here, kid.
o你
She'd want you to have that.
她希望你留著它的
You're the one she cared for.
她真正在乎的是你
Slade...
Slade啊...
Hey, Ollie, just give him space.
嘿 Ollie 他一人o一o
I can't keep lying to him, Sara.
我不能再_他了 Sara
I need to tell him how Shado really died.
我要告V她Shado死亡的真相
Ivo killed Shado. He pulled the trigger.
是Ivo_⒘Shado
Because I chose to save you.
因槲疫x窬饶
He needs to know the truth.
他需要知道真相
- Wait, Ollie, he...  - Get off me.
- 等等 Ollie 他...  - 放_我
He has the mirakuru in his system now.
他手YF在有奇E
What does that have to do with anything?
那又有什NPS?
Look, the Japanese, they experimented
日本人在成千上百人身上
on hundreds of men working to develop mirakuru.
做才研u出了奇E
and I read the research.
我x^他的蟾
The people who died?
那些死去的人?
They were the lucky ones.
他算是幸\的
The ones who survived, they were deformed.
那些活下淼娜 身陷缺
Either their bones or their minds.
身w和精神上的缺
They became someone else.
他得面目全非
You summoned me here for a drink?
你叫我^砭褪榱撕染?
You certainly look dressed for it.
看砟氵打扮了一番
No, I... have a date.
不 我... 要去s
What are you working on?
你在忙什N呢?
Something to do with Sebastian Blood.
我在{查Sebastian Blood
AKA the next mayor of Starling city.
f他是Starling市的下一任市L
Well, maybe he shouldn't be.
也S他不上
- What does that mean?  - I've just been doing
- @怎v?  - 我做了一些
some investigating. Blood had a connection
{查 Bloodcm福德精神病W研究所
to the Langford Psychiatric Institute.
有c瓜葛
The one that burnt down under very
就是那被神秘
mysterious circumstances.
S的研究所
- Do the police suspect arson?  - No.
- 警察抓到v火犯了?  - ]有
They're saying that it's inconclusive.
警察f{查毫oY果
But Blood also knew Cyrus Gold...
而且BloodJRCyrus Gold...
the man that shot and killed four police officers.
他曾_打死四警察
Laurel, where are you going with this?
Laurel 你要把@些ol看?
I don't know. But I do have to go.
不知道 但我得走了
I'm going to be late.
我要t到了
So who's the lucky guy?
l今晚有幸c你相s?
Sebastian Blood.
是Sebastian Blood
He's the man we need to see in the mayor's office. So, please, join me in our efforts
他s膺市L 大家c我一起
to send Starling's favorite son there.
g迎Starling市之子
To Sebastian Blood. Sebastian for Starling.
Sebastian Blood乾杯 xx他ьIStarling市
Thank you, Oliver.
xx Oliver
And not just for your support,
不H是因槟ξ业闹С
but also for your friendship.
更是榱宋的友x
And thank all of you for coming.
感x大家的到
You know, when Oliver calls me a son of Starling city,
才OliverQ我Starling市之子
it feels like the literal truth.
@诱f的_]e
I was a street orphan,
我曾是o家可w的孤
and this city raised me as one of its own.
是@座城市B育了我
I am the man that I am today because of my Starling city family.
我能有今天的一切 都是因Starling市@大家庭的椭
So it's time that I start to give back.
所以我有所回罅
So thank you all for your support.
xx你的支持
Nice speech, Ollie.
演v很精彩 Ollie
Who knew you cared so much about politics?
你什Nr候φ治感d趣了?
Well, I care about the city, and...
哦 我P心@座城市 而且...
Sebastian has become something of a friend.
SebastianF在算是我的朋友
He's got a way of doing that, apparently.
很@然 他混的如~得水
That's very cute.
一c]e
Speaking of which, how's Roy?
哦 α Roy怎N?
Handsome, brooding, usual.
是那N英俊 深沉
Why is my boyfriend such a topic of interest?
你怎NP心起砦夷信笥蚜?
Well, Thea, his idol put an arrow in him, and I just...
哦 Thea 他的偶像o了他一支箭 我只是...
wanted to make sure there weren't any lingering issues.
想知道]遇到其他的麻┌
Oh, my god. Now that I think about it,
天啊 你@Nf我才lF
you know, he did something completely out of character this morning.
他今天早上做了一件很奇怪的事情
What?
什N事?
He showed up for work on time.
他按r砩习嗔
Thea! Oh, it's...
Thea! 哦...
it's just wonderful.
派μ棒了
Proud to my civic duty.
很高d能M到市民的任
No, I'm the one who's proud.
我真槟泸傲
You've taken Oliver's... hobby, and turned it into
你把Oliver的... 酆米成了
a successful business.
一成功的事I
- Hobby?  - Oh, sweetheart.
- 酆?  - 哦
Oliver.
Oliver啊
Ah.
啊
Thank you so much for your kind words.
xx你才的Q
I'm just speaking the truth.
我只是f
Oh, forgive me, a friend just walked in.
哦 失陪一下 有朋友砹
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
Glad you could come.
很高d你能
Sebastian invited me.
Sebastian邀了我
Yes, I hear the two of you have been spending a lot of time together.
是的 我f你z整天在一起
We're just friends.
我只是朋友
Does he know that?
他也@N想?
Uh-oh.
啊哦
What's holding you back?
你有什N可q豫的?
Sometimes I feel like I don't know the real Sebastian.
有r候我摸不透Sebastian
He reminds me a little of you that way.
他我想起了你
Hmm.
嗯
Freedom.
自由
Liberty.
立
Justice.
正x
Long have the people of this city suffered
人已被腐〉恼府
under the shackles of a corrupt government...
自私自利的政客...
slaves to self-interested politicians
有傀儡般的[f者
and their lobbyist puppeteers.
折磨得蜷Lrg了...
I declare war on them all.
我向你所有人宣
Anyone in the building?
大茄Y有人?
Cleaning crew and a group of bankers
有清工和一些上晚班的
working out a late night deal.
y行工作人T
Can you patch me into police and fire?
能臀疫M入警察局和消防的Wj?
I'm on it.
@就M
Diggle...
Diggle啊...
Hey, man, this is not my thing.
嘿 兄弟 我可不擅LX
Can't get up there. Everything's blocked.
]法上去 都被困住了
You've still got people on the 19th floor.
19舆有人]出
It's too hot. We're falling back.
囟忍高 我M不去
Help!
救命!
Gary's still back there.
Gary在Y面
Get to safety.
快去安全地
Give me your hand.
伸手^
Thank you.
xx
Hey.
嘿
You ok?
你好吧?
Where you going?
你要去哪?
To the plane, to get geared up.
去l语wC
For what?
槭颤N?
Ivo is still out there.
Ivo在@Y
I'm going to find him, and when I do,
我要去找他
I'm going to cut pieces of him.
我要把他撕成碎片
You can't. Ivo has a ship
你不能去 Ivo有一船的手下
full of men, of killers. And I don't care
他都是⑹ 不管你以前
what you did before, you can't take them all out.
有多英勇 你不能以一百
Your only play here is to find safe ground and wait him out.
你F在找安全的地方躲著 等他F身
Well, of course you would say that.
你然@Nf
You were working for him.
你樗u命
You're probably still working for him!
你在樗u命
Hey, hey!
嘿 嘿!
She's not.
她不是的
Get out of my way, kid.
er著我 小子
Look, let's just take it easy...
我先冷o一下
I said...
我f了...
get out of my way.
er著我
You ok? Long night.
你]事吧? 昨晚很累吧
Yeah. News report said the bomber didn't steal any money.
嗯 新上f爆炸犯]有偷X
I think this guy just wants to make a statement.
我想他只是想昭告天下
That went online an hour ago.
一小r前W上就鞑ラ_砹
His manifesto. 300 pages of anti-government hate.
他l表了足足300反政府明
You think this psycho's any way connected to our psycho in the skull mask?
你X得@子跟那骷t面具男有PS?
This guy has a completely separate agenda.
@人是为行
He's a lone wolf, but we need
他是匹狼
to find him before he finds his next target.
但是我必在他i定下目饲罢业剿
I'd start with the bomb. Everyone's unique.
我恼上_找索 每人都是一o二的
Maybe we can get some kind of signature on the guy.
也S能找到有P他的索
But the bomb residue is with the SCPD.
但是片N在警察手Y
Fortunately we have an in with one of the officers at the department.
幸\的是 我在警局Y有
I thought you were staying in central city for a few more days.
我以槟氵要在中心城多留滋炷
I got a news alert about the bombing.
我看到了P於爆炸的新
Caught the first train out this morning.
坐著今早的第一班火就s回砹
Good.
太好了
We need you here.
我需要你
How's Barry?
Barry的r如何?
Ah, he's still sleeping.
呃 在昏睡中
I prefer sleeping to coma,
我比^喜g用昏睡 而不用昏迷
because coma sounds, you know, not fun.
因榛杳月起聿凰
I'll reach out to detective Lance.
我去MLance警探
Hey.
嘿
- Did we have a lunch today?  - No.
- 我s好吃午了?  - ]有
I was just in the neighborhood.
我好在附近
Thought I'd stop by. But if this is
想戆菰L一下 要是不巧的
a bad time, I mean, I can always come back.
我其他rg再
Oh, no, not at all, they're still setting up out there.
]有 他在阎
Wow.
哇哦
This is pretty impressive for a street orphan.
真是一位人刮目相看的街^孤喊
Are you suggesting I spread it on a bit too thick last night?
你是不是X得我昨晚的言o有c^了?
No.
]有
It's just...
只是...
Laurel, if there's something on your mind,
Laurel 要是有什N事情
Give it voice.
管直f
I don't bite.
我不介意
I promise.
我f算
- You know my father's with the department.  - Yes.
- 你也知道我父H在警局工作  - 是的
He said the suspect that he was investigating
他f他和他的同事遇ur
when he and his partner were attacked
{查的那嫌疑人
was a man named Cyrus Gold.
叫做Cyrus Gold的人
Cyrus Gold...
Cyrus Gold啊...
was a preacher
曾是牧
at the orphanage where I was raised.
他r在我被收B的孤涸汗ぷ
Cyrus was a very good friend to me...
Cyrus那r是我最好的朋友...
like an older brother.
就像兄L一哟我
Or even a father figure, to be honest.
f 他更像位L者
He was the first person I said a word to,
他曾是我第一意_口v的人
and this was after a month of not speaking at all.
r我已一月]_口v^了
You talk a lot about being an orphan,
你常f起孤r的v
But you don't talk about your parents.
但是s]提起^你的父母
Did you know them?
你λ有何t解?
My father was a very unhappy man.
我父H是d的人
One night he came home soaked in whiskey.
有天晚上 他喝了很多威士忌酒回家
He lost his job again, so he broke her arm.
他又把工作G了 所以他打嗔宋夷赣H的手臂
I tried to stop him, but he threw me off.
我想要阻止他 s被他推到一
And the next thing I saw was my mother holding my father's gun in her hand.
之後就看到母H拿著他的
And I watched her shoot him.
我H眼看著母H向他_
She panicked.
她恐慌O了
Ran and was gone before the police even arrived.
在警察到碇前就匆匆逃跑
It was the last time I saw my parents.
那是我最後一次到他
I'm so sorry.
很抱歉
I don't know...
我不知道...
why Cyrus' life took the turn that it did,
Cyrus楹成@
I'm sad to say.
很抱歉
All I know...
我只知道...
is that he helped a very young,
他曾椭^一恐慌o助的小男孩
very frightened boy find his voice again.
他重新_口v
Ahem. I'm sorry.
抱歉
More later?
晚c好?
发票
l票
圣沃克医院
}沃克t院
Maya Resik
支付人 Sebastian Blood Starling市Oakwood街5531 ] 98114
Didn't hear you come in.
我都]到你M砹
Yeah, sorry, I... I got here early.
抱歉 我... 我碓缌
I just want to get these crates unpacked before lunch.
我就是想在午之前把@些箱子拆好
Are you ok?
你好吧?
Yeah, I'm fine.
是啊 我挺好的
Just... I haven't been sleeping much lately.
只是... 最近睡眠有c不足
I got a lot on my mind.
X子Yy七八糟的
You want to talk about it?
想跟我聊聊?
Talk about what?
聊什N?
Whatever's been going on with you the last five weeks.
^去五周Y你身上l生的事
Look, I'm fine.
看啊 我不挺好的
Ever since the Arrow shot you,
自谋痪G箭b射後
you've been acting really weird, Roy.
你就得怪怪的 Roy
With me, with everything.
o是ξ 是其他事
This isn't about the Arrow.
不PG箭b的事
Is it me?
是因槲?
Is it us?
是我之g怎N了?
Look, I really just want to get through this, ok?
我f 我真的只是想M快恢驼常 好?
Ok.
好的
Let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
有需要我兔Φ 管_口
Thea.
Thea啊
You do help.
你一直在臀
Every day.
一直都在
And honestly, right now you're the only thing
不得不f F在你是唯一
that's keeping me together.
能我不崩⒌娜
I do what I can.
我只是M力而
How did I get to be so lucky?
我怎N@N幸\呢?
You... stole my purse.
因... 你偷了我的包
Hmm.
]e
Roy?!
Roy啊?!
- Thea,are you ok?  - Yeah.
- Thea 你]事吧?  - ]事
Oh, your arm...
天啊 你的手臂...
Um, that looks really deep.
呃 口看起砗苌
It might need stitches. Um, I'm going to go downstairs
可能需要p 我去窍履眉本认
and get the first aid kit, ok?
你能行?
Ok.
]事
You know, most cops,
大多稻察
they meet their informants in the backseat of a cruiser
都是在巡的後座跟人面
or maybe a coffee shop or something, but...
或者是咖啡^什N的 但是...
What's with the mask?
你怎N戴上面具了?
- Gift from a friend.  - You got friends?
- 朋友送的  - 你竟然有朋友?
Did you bring me what I asked for?
我要的|西砹?
That's a sample of everything the CSU collected from the blast.
Y面有取C部T在爆炸F稣业剿有|西的颖
There's melted glass, multiple explosive fragments,
有融化了的玻璃 爆炸物的碎片
and trace residue, and it looks like nitroglycerine.
有爆破物料 看起硐裣趸甘油
Which means that we're dealing with more than just a basement nutjob.
看起聿幌袷普通的子在作案
Someone with training.
他受^
Thank you, detective.
xx你 警探
I need a favor, too.
我也需要你忙
The son of a bitch who killed my men, my partner...
⑺牢彝事和搭n的那罪f死的人...
He's dead.
他死了
And whoever tipped him off, told him we were coming,
有o他通L笮诺娜
he's doing just fine.
他]事
What do you need?
需要我做什N?
Cell phone records for every cop in my precinct.
我^所有警察的通
You think there's a leak in the department?
你X得有裙?
I think those phone records are the only way
我X得通能一切明t
to know for sure, and your blonde friend,
你的那位金朋友
she's pretty good with computers.
她的X技g不是很好嘛
I'll ask her...
我找她兔Φ...
Dc-52 to central, 10-80, downtown!
Dc-52向局R 市中心l生爆炸!
He's hit again.
他又行恿
Starling city municipal building.
Starling市行政大
- Give me a location.  - I'll give you one better...
- 地址告V我  - 我o你比地址有用的...
I'm checking the surrounding cell towers.
我正在搜索附近的信塔
There was a GSM spike
爆炸前擅腌
of 3,800 megahertz two seconds before the blast.
曾出F3800兆赫的定位}n
That frequency's way outside the approved frequency
@l率甚至比
for U.S. Carriers.
美航\l率高
Signal's moving. I think he's mobile.
信在D移 他乘了交通工具
Give me an intersection.
地址o我
Right in front of you, 400 meters.
你正前方400米
I see him.
我看到他了
Turn left on 67th.
第67街左D
Felicity, I've lost him.
Felicity 我跟G了
What?
什N?
Me, too, hold on.
我也是 等下
Got him. Bank left on Gerrard street.
lF他了 Gerrard街左D
You're almost right on top of him.
你差不多就在他正上方
It's not him, Felicity. You picked up the wrong signal.
不是他 Felicity 你的信定位e了
What? I thought... he must have scrambled the signal.
什N? 我以... 他一定是干_信了
It doesn't matter.
o所^了
He is gone.
他逃掉了
What happened?
到底怎N回事?
He's using cellular technology to detonate his bombs.
他使用蜂C技g引爆炸
Clearly, his expertise extends to obscuring that signal.
而且 他很擅L[藏信
Felicity, your expertise was supposed to trump his.
Felicity 你的能力比他啊?
Excuse me?
你什N意思?
If you have something to say to me, Oliver, say it.
有直f Oliver
People are dying. So I would like you to pull your head
人的性命危在旦夕 希望你能虬阉季w闹行某鞘栈
out of central city and get back in the game.
@Y的事上上心
Sure, right after you get yours out of your ass.
是先把你的^w理清吧
- Excuse me?  - All right.
- 你f什N?  - 蛄
Maybe we should just take a breath here.
大家淡定一下
No, wait, I want to know, what exactly was that crack
不行 我要弄明白 你提中心城
about central city meant to imply?
到底是什N意思?
When the first bomb went off, you weren't here.
第一起爆炸案l生的r候 你不在@Y
And when the second bomb went off, you sent me the wrong way.
第二起爆炸案l生的r候 你又o我指e了路
After you didn't catch him in the first place!
是你先跟G了的!
Don't blame me because you didn't have it tonight.
e因槟愕氖д`埋怨我
I need some air.
我出去透透透
At the risk of me getting my head knocked off...
冒著掉^的危U也得f句啊...
Playing the blame game's not going to help us
互相埋怨可不能
catch this son of a bitch.
椭我抓到他
Neither is doing things halfway.
半途而U也不能
Is that what you think's going on here, Oliver?
你X得她@ Oliver?
You think she was distracted?
你X得她不上心?
She wasn't giving it her all?
她]有M心M力?
She almost ran me into a bus, Diggle.
她差c我撞到公交上 Diggle
What do you think?
你X得呢?
I think you didn't have a problem
我X得你是因Barry Allen
with Felicity's performance until she met Barry Allen.
才埋怨Felicity的B
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
You're not well, Slade.
你很不正常 Slade
Hey...
我知道了
It's the mirakuru.
是奇E水
It's messing with your head.
它_y了你的思S
It's going to be dark soon. We should make camp.
天快黑了 我得soI
What's going on? You ok?
怎N了? 你好吧?
Yeah, it's just, arm still hurts when it's cold.
]事 只不^一受龈觳簿吞
And I lost the pain meds that the doctor gave me.
t生o的止疼我o弄G了
How's yours healing up?
你的怎N恿?
Ah, you know, good days and bad.
r好r
I'll see you later.
等聊
Hey.
嘿
Pretty crazy.
不可思h
Yeah. You doing all right?
是啊 你好吧?
I thought I could use your help, if you have a second.
你要是有空的 忙
You being at the DA's office now,
你F在是地^z察官了
it's almost like you joined the family business. Come on.
就像家事一 ^
I'm trying to find someone
我在找一叫"Maya Resik"的人
named "Maya Resik." I searched the internet,
我在W上搜^
the dmv records, social security... nothing.
查了管所和社保 ]有任何信息
Why are you looking for a ghost?
找@右鬼魂致?
Sebastian's paying her bills.
Sebastian在o她X
A woman who doesn't seem to exist,
一不存在的女人
I find that suspicious.
我X得很可疑
Thinking that your boyfriend's up to no good,
你男朋友不押靡
that's typically more my thing than yours.
我比你上心
Oh, he's not exactly my boyfriend.
蚀_地f 他不是我男朋友
Well, that makes digging into his life
那Q探他的生活
a little less fun, then.
也就失去了些啡
Hey, Laurel.
等等 Laurel
If I bring you something back,
如果我湍悴槌鳇c|西
you know I'm going to want to know why.
我要知道槭颤N
Of course you are.
你的
Ah, you're just in time to see the show.
你回淼恼是r候 好s上表演
What's he doing?
他在?
Bringing the city together.
把整城市的人聚集起
And if I'm not mistaken, campaigning.
要是我]弄e的 x
Tomorrow night, I am holding starling's first ever unity rally at city plaza.
明天晚上 我要在城市大B召_第一次合大
We are going to show the world that the people of this great city
我要向世界C明 @座ゴ蟪鞘械娜嗣
will not back down to terrorists.
不向恐怖萘νf
He's committing suicide and he just invited
他想自
the entire city to join him.
要叫上全市的人和他一起
Sebastian's your friend.
你是Sebastian的朋友
Can't you talk him out of this, Oliver?
你能不能袼?
Well, that day is now.
就是今天
Well, he won't listen to me.
他不我的
Sebastian Blood...
Sebastian BloodhT...
This rally tomorrow night,
明晚的集
you need to call it off.
你要取消
The starling city vigilante paying a visit to wave me off.
G箭bH自斫o我送行
I'm flattered.
我很s幸
This event, Mr. Blood,
Mr. Blood @次集
You might as well be painting a giant bulls eye on your chest.
你知道 是玩火自焚
This city needs to come together.
@座城市需要FY
And I need to show them how.
而我告V他怎N做
You won't be able to show them anything if you're dead.
你死了 就什N都做不了
Every night, you risk your life
每天晚上 你冒著生命危U
for the people of this city.
保l@座城市的人民
How can you expect me to do any less?
我怎N能作壁上^?
And what about the lives of the people coming to your rally?
你就不⒓蛹人的生命?
This rally is about Starling City
@次集
standing up and declaring with one voice
是要Starling市起
that living afraid isn't living.
告V人恐种械纳活不能叫生活
I won't send a contrary message to people
我不告V市民待在家Y
telling them to stay home, to stay scared.
@受怕
I've made my decision.
我意已Q
That's the thing, Alderman...
好了 hT
Whatever happens tomorrow night,
明晚l生的事
it's not up to you.
K非你能Q定的
# I wake up and she's not there #
# 我醒砹 而她已不在 #
Ah, Mrs. Fazekas.
是Fazekas女士啊
The train set for your nephew
o你外甥涞幕疖到
just came in. He's going to love it.
他一定鬯懒
Oh. You are a miracle worker, Mr. Scheffer.
您真是太敬I了 Scheffer先生
How much do I owe you?
我o你多少X?
$50 even.
50就好
Forget the sales tax.
N售就不用了
Going to the alderman's unity rally tomorrow night?
明晚去⒓幼hT的集?
I wouldn't miss it.
然不e^
Gathered here despite the rash of bombings
o爆炸o城市淼睦_
that have plagued the city,
而聚集在@Y
Some have called Sebastian Blood's unity rally
有人fSebastian Blood召_的@次集
a cynical and dangerous pr stunt
是他榱烁x市LM的
for his mayoral campaign.
一次危U而不任的公P噱^
But the crowd continues to grow.
但是⑴c的人颠在增加
Tried to get him to stand down.
我襁^他了
He seems as stubborn as you when it comes to fighting back.
他回舻r候和你一庸
- Or everything.  - Hey, is this how
- 不光是回舻r候  - 是不以後
it's going to be with you two from now on?
你z就一直@恿?
Maybe we should just head down to the rally.
我去集F
Maybe we won't have to.
不一定要去
I analyzed the bomb remnants we got from Lance.
我分析了Lanceo的爆炸留物
The design's identical to the bombs used by
它的O和以前叫行拥姆凑府民兵部
an anti government militia group called the Movement.
所使用的炸一
Lucky for us, they have a very active and hackable message board.
幸\的是 我可以黑M他活S的留言板
One of their most prolific fans has an ip address right here in Starling.
其中一很多a的粉z的IP地址就在Starling
- Tell me.  - The computer's in a local souvenir shop.
- 在哪?  - 那台X在一家o念品商店
The whackadoo in question goes by the username Shrapnel.
所找少年的用裘叫Shrapnel
You want back-up?
需要後援幔
No, I need you at the rally.
不 你去集
Cover our bases.
掩o我的基地
Is this all for me?
@都是o我的?
No, for me. SCPD phone records.
不 是我的 警察局的通
Why are you going through the department's phone records?
你槭颤N要查警局的通?
Um, so I checked up on your not exactly boyfriend.
我查了你那不算男朋友的男朋友
And? Did you find anything?
然後呢? 有什NlF?
Yeah, it turns out he's a hell of a guy.
然 我lF他不是好人
Covers the expenses of his dear aunt...
替她姑姑付X...
Your Maya Resik.
他姑姑就是Maya Resik
If Sebastian has other family,
如果Sebastian有其他家人
then why was he placed in an orphanage?
那他槭颤N在孤涸?
Well, maybe 'cause aunt Maya is nuttier than a snickers bar.
也S是他的Maya姑姑X子有}
She's a patient at St.Walker's hospital.
她是}沃克斯t院的病人
It's a mental institution, it's the kind you don't check out of.
那是家精神病院 你根本不去查的地方
Now, listen, you going to tell me what this is all about?
你到底要不要告V我l生了什N?
Something about him just seems off.
他似乎不太正常
Laurel, there is nothing sinister
Laurel 替自己唯一
about a guy who is covering the expenses
在世的H人付X
of his only living relative.
]什N比@更可怕的了
The truth is, it's kind of nice.
而事是 @很好
Listen, I gotta get to city plaza.
我要去城市大B了
Pike wants all hands at this unity rally.
Pike要召集所有人手
You're not going, right?
你不去的 Π?
No, I need to look into this more.
我不去了 我要^m深入{查
Laurel, he seems like a good guy
Laurel 他看起硎好孩子
and you deserve good.
他配得上你
Ok, so stop looking for reasons
emY於@些
to talk yourself out of it.
又把自己撇出去了
Please.
求你了
Alderman Blood, is this not dangerous?
BloodhT @很危U你知道?
I'm afraid so.
恐怕是的
Why are you gathering all these people here to be targets?
你槭颤N要把@N多人聚集在@活靶子?
Please, I'll get to all of your questions later.
稍後我一一回答你的}
Thank you all for coming.
感x你能
Boom.
砰
You're dead.
你已死了
Or will be if you take one more step
你敢往前走一步
or move a single muscle.
或者稍微右幌戮驼嫠懒
And then you'll miss the show.
那你就看不到接下淼谋硌萘
Candidate Blood's unity rally.
候x人Blood的集
Already rigged with 50 pounds of RDX high explosives.
我在那貉b好了50磅的烈性旋L炸
Not unlike what's packed inside the drywall of my store.
和我店Y石膏板後b的可不一
This city thinks Sebastian Blood can keep them safe.
市民X得Sebastian Blood能保C他的安全
Tonight, they learn that the only thing politicians
今晚 他明白
care about protecting is their jobs.
政治家只P心他的前途
- Felicity.  - Here.
- Felicity  - 在
Did you get him?
你抓住他了?
No. He said he rigged the plaza
]有 他f他的爆炸b置
with an explosive device.
能炸д大
Oliver, it's crazy-town there.
Oliver 那人山人海
That bomb could be anywhere.
炸可能在任何地方
I can narrow that down. Get me Diggle.
我能s小 o我接通Diggle
Go.
f吧
Shrapnel said he ringed the perimeter with RDX.
Shrapnelf他在周b好了旋L炸
I'm on it.
我去找
You're heading to the plaza, too, right?
你在去大B的路上吧?
Not yet.
]有
I need you to pull me up anything you can on the store.
我要你把P於@商店所有的|西找出
Blue prints, permit schematics, anything.
OD 示意D 所有|西
What's going on?
怎N了?
Shrapnel left behind a surprise.
Shrapnelo我留了@喜
Said he packed the drywall with explosives,
f他在石膏板後也放好了炸
but the trigger needs to be...
但是要|l需要...
Would need to be hooked up to some sort of power supply.
需要B接到源
That's assuming that the detonator's connected
Щ鹚鬟B接到商店的路
to the store's electricity and not something independent
而且不是汽池那N立的流
like a car battery. I know, not helpful.
我明白 但是]什N椭
You sure you want me doing this?
你_定要我做@?
My head might not exactly be in the game.
我的思路可能不在@鲷Y里
Felicity!
Felicity! e[!
The building was built in the seventies.
那鞘70年代建的
That's good news.
@是好消息
The wiring in a lot of construction back then is defective.
那r的建BY路有很多缺陷
So if you sever one wire,
如果你切嗔艘l
it will blow fuses in the entire building
就嗾堑谋ｋUz
and shot off power to the bomb.
然後切嗾的源
Hold tight. I see a fuse box.
注意了 我看保U盒了
Oliver, be careful.
Oliver 小心c
Oliver?
Oliver 你在?
It's all right. I'm all right.
]事 我]事
Get to the rally.
去集吧
Help Diggle. I'm on my way.
去Diggle 我@就去
Thea, I really don't think coming here was a good idea.
Thea 我真X得不磉@Y
It's gonna be fine.
不有事的
Let's just go find Roy.
我去找Roy
Please, please.
安o
You're the ones who deserve an ovation.
o你鼓掌喝彩
8 months ago this city survived a devastating attack...
8月前 @座城市缧缘囊u糁写婊钕...
But we rose up.
但是我站起砹
You rose up
你站起砹
and banded together, just like we are tonight.
K且FY起 就像今晚一
Dig, I'm on site.
Dig 我到了
I'm on the east side. Think I found the trigger.
我在| 是找到|l器了
And prove to the world
K向全世界C明
that we cannot be broken.
我是打不倒的
That the people of this city
@座城市的人
are too strong.
非常
And that no bomb and no earthquake
不是炸和地震
is strong enough to tear us apart.
就能摧У
Oliver said that the whole place
Oliverf@地方
was ringed with explosives.
到都是炸
It's in the sound equipment.
在@音O溲Y
and this is the trigger.
@就是|l器
Shrapnel activates it by cellular transmission.
Shrapnel通^手C信铀
Listen, we don't have to disarm it, just disable it.
著 ]必要拆除它 U掉它就行
I can do that.
我可以
I think.
我想是的
I hope.
希望是
Felicity, listen, you be careful.
Felicity 好 你要小心
He probably put in a safeguard.
他也S用了保障措施
Tampering with it
M行干A
will set off a deadman's switch.
也S|l死人I
That's a really depressing term.
那~真阂
And a little bit sexist.
而且有性e歧之嫌
Step away.
走_
Or we all know how this ends.
否tl都活不成
Dig!
Dig啊!
Mom!
!
I'm OK. I'm OK.
我]事 我]事
Drop the bow.
把弓放下
I've got charges planted all over Starling.
我在Starling市埋M了炸
I drop this stick, they all blow.
我按了@ 就爆炸
Did you just hear what I said?
你到我才f的了?
Yep.
到了
Hey.
嘿
How's your mom?
你怎N恿?
She's fine. Just a little shooken up.
她]事 有c到了
You saved her.
你救了她
I got lucky.
是我走\
That wasn't luck.
那不是\
That was impossible.
那直不可能
You know those stories of mom's lifting cars to save their kids?
你知道有把抬起砭茸约旱暮⒆?
Things you can do when adrenaline hits.
I上腺素j升r 啥都能做到
It was... It was one of those.
我... 我就是那
Your arm.
你的手臂
There's not even a mark.
B疤痕都]留下
It's... I heal fast.
是... 我口K合快
- It's fine.  - Right.
- ]事  - 嗯
I'm kind of tired. It's been a long night, you know.
我有c累了 今天晚上太多事了
I gotta go.
我走了
Roy.
Roy啊
With you dropping fewer bodies,
你⒌娜嗽碓缴
Starling city should probably build a bigger jail.
Starling市大概建一大c的Oz
Another night of skull mask hunting?
又要去找骷t面具人?
Not exactly.
不是
How's your shoulder?
你肩膀怎恿?
Oh, just a through-and-through.
不乐
Walk in the park.
小意思
Still, Diggle, you should go home and get some rest.
但是Diggle 你是回家休息一下
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
Are you apologizing to me
你在向我道歉
or were you talking to your quiver?
是在跟你的箭袋f
I didn't snap at my quiver.
我又]跟我箭袋l脾
You kind of more than snapped.
你不止是l脾獍
I know.
我知道
And I'm sorry.
很抱歉
I understand that this mirakuru thing has you freaked out
我知道奇E的事你很害怕
and I have been in central city a lot.
而我又在中心城待了太久
Felicity, it's not that.
Felicity 不是因槟
When you are there,
你在那Y的r候
Well, it just made me realize how much I need you here.
就更我意R到 @Y多需要你
In the beg... beginning,
_... _始的r候
I was just gonna... I was gonna do all of this by myself.
我... 我渥约鹤鲞@些事
And now with you and Diggle...
如今有了你和Diggle...
I rely on you.
我依你
Does that mean I have a shot
那是否意味著
at employee of the month?
我有可能成槊餍lT呢?
No.
不是
Because you're not my employee.
因槟悴皇俏业T工
You're my partner.
你是我的同伴
Barry's gonna wake up.
Barry醒淼
And when he does, you will be there.
他醒r 你要在他身
I finally have a guy who's interested in me
K於有人喜g我了
and he's struck by lightning,
他s被W糁辛
ends up in a coma.
於昏迷中
Typical.
真神奇
Well, maybe he's dreaming about you.
也S他舻侥隳
You know, actually there's conflicting cases
知道 於於昏迷的病人
about whether coma patients can in fact dream normally
是真的在做暨是a生幻X
Or they're more like hallucinating.
不能_定
Thank you.
xx
Sara.
Sara啊
Sara, I know you're listening. Answer me.
Sara 我知道你在 回答我
This is very simple, Sara.
事情非常 Sara
I know you and your new friends have the mirakuru.
我知道你和你的新朋友有奇E
You know I will lay waste to this entire island to get it.
就算⑦@Y夷槠降 我也要得到它
Get Slade.
去叫Slade
But it doesn't have to be that way.
但不必那
All I want is the serum.
我只想要血清
In exchange, I'll promise you and your friends
作榻Q 我可以向你和你的朋友保C
safe passage off this island, I promise.
你可以安全x_@u
Within 10 days, you and your new friends
十天之 你和你的新朋友
could be making port in Shanghai.
就可以到_上海
The alternative is I send my men
我也可以派我的手下
into the jungle to take the serum from you.
到擦盅Y找到你 拿到血清
They'll be under orders not to kill any of you.
他奉我的命令 不⒛
Instead, you'll remain alive enough
反而 你活著
for me to indulge my scientific curiosity.
M足我的科W好奇心
Think about it, Sara.
考]一下吧 Sara
- He's gone.  - What?
- 他走了  - 什N?
Slade's gone and he took the mirakuru with him.
Slade走了 把奇E也ё吡
You can ask all the questions you want,
你可以任何}
but I wouldn't count on getting anything back.
但是估也不出什N
She probably won't even know you're there.
她也S都不知道你在她身
I'll be down the hall if you need anything.
如果你需要什N 我就在窍
Maya?
Maya啊?
I'm here to talk about your nephew.
我砀你P於你侄子的事
Un buen chico.
有一男孩
Maya, my name's Laurel Lance.
Maya 我叫Laurel Lance
Maya?
Maya啊?
I'm here to talk about your nephew.
我砀你P於你侄子的事
Un buen chico,
有一男孩
Maya? Maya, que chico?
Maya? Maya 知道?
Que chico? Sebastian?
知道? Sebastian?
Sebastian.
Sebastian啊
Yes, yes. Sebastian Blood.
是的 是的 Sebastian Blood
There will always be those who seek to harm us,
有人要害我
but it will not weaken us.
但那不我弱
It will only make us stronger.
那只我更大
Well done, Alderman.
做得好 hT
Thanks to you.
多了你
Still a very big risk to take.
但是冒了很大的U
Tonight we both stood up for Starling city.
今晚我一同支持Starling市
You and me, we can save this city,
你和我 如果我合作
if we work together.
就可以拯救@城市
Maya, can you talk to me about Sebastian?
Maya 你能跟我ffSebastian的事?
It's OK. You can trust me.
]事的 你可以信任我
OK?
好?
Sebastian is my friend.
Sebastian是我的朋友
Sebastian is the devil.
Sebastian是耗
He the one who put me here.
他把我扔到@Y
He made everybody think I'm insane.
他所有人J槲爷了
But why would he do that?
但是他槭颤N那N做?
He killed his father.
他⒘俗约旱母赣H
And I was there.
我r在
I saw it.
我看了
Oh, my god.
天啊
Sebastian isn't your nephew,
Sebastian不是你的侄子
he's your son.
他是你鹤
Don't trust a word he says.
不要相信他的
You can't trust Sebastian Blood.
^不能相信Sebastian Blood
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
-=}城家@SCG字幕M http://hd.cnscg.com/=- H供翻g交流使用, 禁止用於商I用途
协调: Tracy 时间轴: 潇妹纸 翻译: 初见 yjk8654 水果哥 Tracy 校对: 潇妹纸
f{: Tracy rgS: t妹 翻g: 初 yjk8654 水果哥 Tracy 校: t妹